Sleeping off the side effects again
I, I double the intake
I like you that way
And it's not the best look to be so thirsty like
But it's all for you
Can I be enough?
Please let me be the promise that you keep
Offering my soul for something real
A sacrifice to feel
Please let me be the weakness in your knees
Part me from my heart, my fate is sealed
A sacrifice so I can feel
Seems you've lost your train of thought again
Don't call me a mistake, don't throw me away
Lies suited you so well
Maybe our time is up, maybe I'm not enough
To give him a reason to know when to leave him
Please let me be the promise that you keep
Offering my soul for something real
A sacrifice to feel
Please let me be the weakness in your knees
Part me from my heart, my fate is sealed
A sacrifice so I can feel
Stop come no closer, so I won't cry
Should have known I'd never mean anything to you
I can see through your disguise
Please let me be the promise that you keep
Offering my soul for something real
A sacrifice to feel
Please let me be the weakness in your knees
Part me from my heart, my fate is sealed
A sacrifice so I can feel